worldofbeer.com 2018-10-06

# World of Beer - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 19, 2017

World of Beer Franchising, Inc. ("WOB," "we," "us," or "our") takes seriously the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes the information collected through this web site and the mobile applications that we provide (together, "Site") and how that information is used and shared. WOB and its suppliers may collect or receive the types of information described below in connection with your access to and use of the Site (together, "Collected Information").

**BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, ACCESSING, OR OTHERWISE USING THE SITE, OR BY ACCEPTING OUR WOB REWARDS TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION AS DISCUSSED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE OR ANY PORTION OF THE SITE.**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of our Terms of Use, our WOB Rewards Terms and Conditions, and any end user license or similar agreement pertaining to any mobile application that WOB provides. We may modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, which changes will be effective immediately upon their posting on the Site. Material changes will be posted conspicuously on the Site. 

If you are visiting the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that Collected Information may be transferred to, stored in, and processed in the United States (where our and our suppliers' servers and databases are located and operated). The data protection and related laws and regulations of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in the country from which you are accessing the Site. If you do not consent to this transfer, do not accept this privacy policy or otherwise use the website.

WOB is the exclusive owner of all Collected Information. In the event of a change in control or reorganization of WOB or sale by WOB of substantially all of its assets, Collected Information may be transferred or sold to such WOB successor. That successor will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy as it applies to that Collected Information.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

You may visit the Site without disclosing any personally identifiable information, but you will be required to provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain Site features, such as requesting to receive our email newsletter, registering with the Site to receive email notifications for WOB locations, purchasing a gift card, requesting to receive more information about franchising opportunities, or joining the WOB rewards program.

WOB will collect any personally identifiable information from or about you that you provide to us, which information may include your name, contact information (including your telephone number, physical address, and email address), shipping information, payment information, and your birthdate. You may choose to submit additional information, which we will collect if you choose to provide it. If you provide your wireless or other telephone number to us, we will use that telephone number to look up your WOB rewards account, if applicable. We will use your personally identifiable information to communicate with you and as otherwise set forth below, subject to applicable laws.

### Mailing List Information

If you sign up or otherwise opt in to receive emailed promotions from us, you will need to submit your name, email address, and birthdate. You must be at least 21 years of age in order to sign up for our mailing lists. We will use this information to provide you with promotional and other communications that we think may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from us at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the applicable email. We may use a third party email provider to deliver these communications to you.

### Rewards Program

If you sign up for the WOB rewards program you will need to submit your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, and birthdate. To register your physical WOB rewards program card on the Site, you will need to enter the loyalty card number located on that card.

If you use the Site while logged into your WOB rewards program account or if you use your WOB rewards program membership at a WOB location, we will collect information about your activity and transactions, for example, the beers you have purchased and the WOB locations you have visited.

### Payment Information

Purchases of gift cards must be made by credit or debit card. All credit and debit card information is provided directly to our PCI-compliant third-party payment processor. WOB does not directly access or handle your credit or debit card information. To make a purchase, you will need to submit your name, email address, and telephone number, as well as your credit or debit card number, expiration date, CVV code, and billing address. Payment by credit or debit card is subject to the approval of the card issuer. We will not be liable in any way if a card issuer refuses to accept a credit or debit card for any reason. We do not store or maintain any credit or debit card information.

### Franchise Inquiries

If you fill out an inquiry form on the Site with respect to WOB franchising opportunities, you will need to submit various information pertaining to the prospective franchisee, such as whether or not you have franchising experience, your areas of interest, and limited company financial information.

When you browse our website, you are able to do so anonymously. However, we may passively collect anonymous information when you are on our website.

### Google Analytics

This web site uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc., to collect information about your use of this web site, which information your web browser automatically sends to Google. This information includes the URLs of the web sites that you visit and your IP address. Google may also set cookies or read preexisting cookies. This information is stored on Google's servers. Google uses this information to provide us with reports about web site traffic and your visits to this web site (for example, the domain from which you access the Internet, the web address of the web site from which you linked to this web site, and the date and time of your visit to the web sites that you view and click through). We will use this data to improve this web site's structure and content. Google may use this data in accordance with its Privacy Policy, which is located at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy. For more information on how Google uses your data, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners. You may opt out of our use of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out web site at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and installing the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On. Please remember that you will need to opt out for each browser you use.

### Cookies

This web site uses cookies to track the use of this web site and to facilitate and enhance your experience on this web site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. This web site may use both cookies that we implement and cookies implemented by our suppliers and other third parties. Cookies enable us to track how you access and use this web site, to learn when and how you and others visit this web site, to learn which pages of this web site are popular and which are not, and to learn which web sites direct you to this web site. Cookies can also help us to improve your enjoyment of this web site, for example, by remembering your contact information when you access this web site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this web site. Our web site suppliers may use cookies and other tracking technologies to track visitors across the Internet to understand how you get to this web site. Due to this automatic collection of cookies, we do not honor "do not track" requests.

### Advertising Networks and Personalized Advertising

The Site uses Google AdWords, an online advertising service provided by Google Inc., to collects anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with the Site and other web sites. Google Inc. will use this information to target advertisements for goods and services. These targeted advertisements may appear on the Site or on other web sites. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a "pixel tag," which is industry-standard technology. To opt out of remarketing advertising provided through Google or to customize your ad preferences, visit Google's Ad Settings page at http://www.google.com/settings/ads. Opting out will not affect your use of the Site. To obtain more information about third-party ad networks and online behavioral advertising and to change your preferences with respect to certain online ads, please visit the National Advertising Initiative Consumer Opt-Out web site at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices or the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Program web site at http://www.aboutads.info. Opting out of online ads with one ad network and web browser does not necessarily carry over to any other ad network or web browser. As a result, depending on the opt-outs you request, you may still see our ads from time to time.

### IP Addresses and Related Data

The servers used to operate the Site may collect data pertaining to you and the equipment, software, and communication methods you use to access the Internet and the Site, including Internet protocol ("IP") addresses assigned to your computer, your Internet service provider (ISP), your approximate geographic location, your browser type, the pages you access on the Site, the web sites you access before and after visiting the Site, the length of time you spend on the Site, date and time stamps, and clickstream data. WOB may use this information to administer the Site and its servers, to generate statistical information, to monitor and analyze Site traffic and usage patterns, to monitor and prevent fraud, to investigate complaints and violations of our policies, and to improve the Site's content and the products, services, materials, and other content that we describe or make available through the Site. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information, other Collected Information, and information obtained from third parties for security reasons. The suppliers that we use to provide the Site may collect information about your visits to the Site and other web sites.

### Geographic Location

We may access your location with your consent in order to enhance your user experience and increase the usefulness of the Site. You may choose to allow us to access your location by granting the Site access to your location when prompted or through your device's location services settings. If you are at a WOB location with Bluetooth or WiFi activated, the WOB location may be able to see your device.

WOB may use various technologies to access your location, including GPS and IP addresses. In addition, WOB uses the Google Places API(s) for location searches and as a result is using the Google Maps/Google Earth API(s). Pursuant to the Google Maps/Google Earth APIs Terms of Service, use of this location feature is also subject to Google's privacy policy, which can be found at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy. Both the Google Maps/Google Earth APIs Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy are incorporated into this Privacy Policy by this reference.

### Social Media

The Site may allow you to connect and share information with various social media platforms, for example, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and Pinterest. These features may require us to implement cookies, plug-ins, and application protocol interfaces (APIs) provided by those social media platforms. We may share information that you provide us or that we may collect about your use of the Site with those platforms and that information will be subject to their privacy policies. For further information, we encourage you to review those platforms' privacy policies: Facebook's Data Policy at https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy; Instagram's Privacy Policy at https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy; Twitter's Privacy Policy at https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en; and Pinterest's Privacy Policy at https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy.

### Embedded Content

The Site incorporates content, including feeds scripts embedded in the Site's code as well as visible content (for example, videos) provided by third parties. In some cases, those third parties collect data about how you interact with their content. For example, YouTube may collect or otherwise have access to usage data on videos embedded on the Site as set forth in YouTube's privacy policy, https://www.google.com/policies/privacy.

In addition to the uses described above, WOB and its suppliers may use and share Collected Information as described below. We will not sell, rent, or share Collected Information except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy or as permitted by applicable law.

### Purpose Collected

We will use your personally identifiable information for the purpose for which you have given it to us, including to communicate with you in connection with your WOB rewards program account, to process your gift card purchases, and to provide you with information and communications that you request. If you register for a rewards program account on the Site, we will use your information to communicate with you regarding your account. If you submit your zip code or complete physical address in order to locate the nearest WOB locations, we will use that information to process that request. If you contact us for support or assistance in using the Site, we may use Collected Information to determine whether or not your system meets the minimum requirements needed to access and use the Site and otherwise to contact you regarding your request. 

### Communication with You

We may use Collected Information to notify you of changes made to the Site, such as changes to our Terms of Use, our WOB Rewards Terms and Conditions, and this Privacy Policy, and, if you sign up or otherwise opt in to receive promotions from us, to send you promotional materials and other communications as set forth above.

### Franchisees

Each individual WOB location may be owned by a franchisee as a separate legal entity from us. As a result, Collected Information may be shared with the individual location. In addition, information that you share with any individual WOB location may be submitted back to WOB.

### Site Evaluation and Improvement

We may use Collected Information: to analyze, develop, and improve the content, materials, products, and services that we make available through the Site and the Site's functionality; to inform marketing and communication plans and strategies; to evaluate user needs and customize Site content, promotional emails, and your browsing experience; and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes.

### Security and Protection of Rights

We may use Collected Information and share it with third parties to the extent permitted by applicable law, including in the event of a subpoena, court order, or law enforcement request. WOB will use Collected Information and share it with third parties if we believe doing so is necessary to operate the Site or to protect our rights or the rights of others, including disclosing information necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action in the event of a violation of our contracts, terms, or policies.

### Sharing Collected Information with Other Third Parties

We may share Collected Information with third parties who have products or services that we think may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving communications from any such third party pursuant to such third party's policies. We do not control any third party or their policies.

### Sharing Collected Information with Our Suppliers

We may share Collected Information with our Site management and hosting supplier, payment processors, online contest management services providers, marketing and public relations service providers, email service suppliers, and other suppliers as necessary for us to provide the Site and our products and services to you and as may otherwise be permitted by applicable law. We require our suppliers to comply with all applicable data privacy laws and regulations. Our suppliers are authorized to and may use Collected Information as necessary for them to provide the applicable services to us.

### Aggregated Information

In addition, we may aggregate personally identifiable information and other Collected Information to create anonymous aggregate information on Site users, which information describes users as a group but does not reveal the identity of individual users. We may use and share aggregated information to determine Site user demographics and usage patterns, to determine what types of products and services we can provide, and to improve and enrich our products, services and Site content. We may also sell, license, or otherwise share anonymous aggregated information with third parties for our own business purposes.

This website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age and WOB does not knowingly collect or use information from children under 13 through the Site.

The Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of information will not occur, WOB uses industry standards, such as Secure Socket Layers ("SSL") technology, to help safeguard against such occurrences. In certain areas, the information passed between your browser and our system is encrypted with SSL technology to create a protected connection between you and our website to ensure confidentiality. The storage and communication of information can never be completely secure, so we do not guarantee that communications or other information that you submit or that are otherwise provided to us will be completely secure. If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us at info@worldofbeerusa.com immediately. In the event that a breach into our security systems occurs, WOB will notify you of the breach only if and to the extent required under applicable law.

If you wish to have access to your personally identifiable information as it exists in our records, please contact us with your request at info@worldofbeerusa.com. You may also request that we update your personally identifiable information or correct any factual errors that you believe may exist regarding this information.

This website may link to, or be linked to, other websites not maintained by or related to WOB. WOB is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or third-party websites, including any linked or linking websites. To the extent that you disclose personally identifiable information to any such third parties, different rules may apply to their use and disclosure of personal information that you disclose to them. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such websites before disclosing your personal information to them.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at info@worldofbeerusa.com, via mail at World of Beer Franchising, Inc., 10910 Sheldon Rd, Tampa, FL 33626, or via telephone at (813) 926-9300.
